Danny Kaye and Sylvia Fine Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 2-627, OV 868)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Music
    - Meyer, George W., Edgar Leslie and E. Ray Goetz
      - For me and my gal. New York: Mills Music, 1945. (Box-folder 438/1)
    - Miller, Bob
      - Conversation with a mule. New York: Bob Miller, Inc., 1935., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/1)
    - Miller, Lost John
      - Rainbow at midnight. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co, Inc. 1946., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/1)
    - Miller, Ned
      - Snow flake. New York: Rondo Music Co., 1959. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Miller, Roger
      - England swings. Nashville: Tree Pub. Co., 1965. (Box-folder 509/1)
      - King of the road. Nashville: Tree Pub. Co. Inc., 1964. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Miller, Sonny
      - Three little kittens. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1952. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Miller, Sy and Jill Jackson
      - High upon a mountain. New York: Edwin H. Morris & Co., Inc., 1955. (Box-folder 438/1)
      - Let there be peace on earth. New York: Jan-Lee Music, 1955., 2 copies (Box-folder 509/1)
      - The Lord loves a laughin' man. New York: Keys-Hansen, Inc., 1956., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/1)
      - People to people. Beverly Hills: Jan-Lee Music, 1966., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/1)
      - Take a moment!. New York: Jan-Lee Music., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/1)
    - Mills, Alan and Rose Bonne
      - I know an old lady. New York: Peer International Corp., 1952. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Mills, Gordon and Les Reed
      - It's not unusual. New York: Leeds Music Co., 1965., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/1)
    - Mills, Irving
      - Boot camp a-go-go. Beverly Hills: Pacsa Music Pub., 1965. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Mills, Kerry, Andrew B. Sterling and Timothy Gray
      - Meet me in St. Louis, Louis. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1960., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/1)
    - Minnigerode, Meade, George S. Pomeroy and Tod B. Galloway
      - The whiffenpoof song. New York: Miller Music Corp., 1936. (Box-folder 438/1, 509/1)
    - Mizzy, Vic and Irving Taylor
      - Kille kille. New York: Santly-Joy-Select, 1942. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Modugno, Domenico
      - Strada 'nfosa. Milano: Edizioni Curci, 1957. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Modugno, Domenico and F. Migliacci
      - Nel blu dipinto di blu. Milano: Edizioni Curci, 1958. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Mohr, Halsey K. and Joe Goodwin
      - They're wearing 'em higher in Hawaii. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1916., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Mohr, Joseph and Frank Gruber
      - Silent night, holy night. New York: Carl Fischer, Inc., 1942. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Monaco, James V. and Johnny Burke
      - Ain't it a shame about Mame. New York: Santly-Joy-Select, 1940. (Box-folder 509/1)
      - An apple for the teacher. New York: Joy Music, Inc., 1939. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - April played the fiddle. New York: Joy Music, Inc., 1940. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - Eastside of heaven. New York: Joy Music, Inc., 1942. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - Hang your heart on a hickory limb. New York: Santly-Joy-Select, Inc., 1939. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - I've got a pocketful of dreams. New York: Joy Music, Inc., 1938. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - A man and his dream. New York: Joy Music, Inc., 1939. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - My heart is taking lessons. New York: Joy Music, Inc., 1938. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - On the sentimental side. New York: Joy Music, Inc., 1938. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - Only forever. New York: Joy Music, Inc., 1940. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - Sing a song of sunbeams. New York: Joy Music, Inc., 1942. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - Sweet potato piper. New York: Santly-Joy-Select, Inc., 1939. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - This is my night to dream. New York: Select Music Pub. Inc., 1938. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Monaco, James V. and Mack Gordon
      - I can't begin to tell you. New York: Bregman, Vocco and Conn., Inc., 1945. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - I'm making believe. New York: Bregman, Vocco and Conn., Inc., 1945. (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Monaco, James and Ted Koehler
      - Ev'ry night about this time. New York: Warock Music, Inc., 1942. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Monaco, James V. and Ballard MacDonald
      - Ten little bottles. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1920. (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Monaco, James V. and Charles Newman
      - Six lessons from Madame LaZonga. New York: Bregman, Vocco and Conn., Inc., 1945. (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Monaco, Jimmie V.
      - Oh, mister dream man. New York: Harry Von Tilzer Music Pub. Co., 1911. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Monaco, Jimmie and William Jerome
      - Row, row, row. Santa Monica: Harry Von Tilzer Music Pub. Co., 1912. (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Monaco, Jimmie and Joe McCarthy
      - Through (How can you say we're through?). New York: Bregman, Vocco and Conn., Inc., 1929. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - If we can't be the same old sweethearts. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1915. (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Monaco, Jimmy, Joe McCarthy and Howard Johnson
      - What do you want to make those eyes at me for?. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1916. (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Monnot, Marguerite, Julian More, David Heneker and Monty Norman
      - Irma la douce. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1958. (Box-folder 509/1)
      - Our language of love. New York: Chappell & Co., Inc., 1956. (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Monnot, Marguerite and Geoffrey Parsons
      - If you love me (really love me). New York: Duchess Music Corp., 1949. (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Monroe, Bill
      - Blue moon of Kentucky. New York: Peer International Corp., 1947. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Moore, Hal and Bill Fredricks
      - Must be Santa. New York: Hollis Music, Inc., 1960., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Moore, James
      - The dacent Irish boy. London: Paterson's Pub. Ltd., 1940. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Moore, Sir Thomas
      - The last rose of summer. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Morales, Noro and Harold Adamson
      - Bim bam boom. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1941. (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Moret, Neil and Richard A. Whiting
      - She's funny that way. San Francisco: Villa Moret, Inc., 1928. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Morgan, Russ and Mack David
      - Sweet Eloise. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1942., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Morgan, Russ, Remus Harris and Irving Melsher
      - So long. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1940., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Moross, Jerome, Morty Neff and Jack Lewis
      - The big country. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1958. (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Moross, Jerome and John LaTouche
      - Lazy afternoon. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1954. (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Morris, John, Gerald Freedman and John Morris
      - Far from home. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1966. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - How green was my valley. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1966. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - I wonder if. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1966. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - Let me love you. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1966. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - There is beautiful you are. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1966. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - A time for singing. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1966. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - When he looks at me. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1966. (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Morse, Theodore and Howard Johnson
      - M-o-t-h-e-r. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1915. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Morton, George, Jeff Barry and Ellie Greenwich
      - Leader of the pack. New York: Tender Tunes Music Co., and Elmwin Music Inc., 1964. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Mozart, W. A.
      - Serenade in four movements. New York: Carl Fischer Inc., 1927. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Mueller, Gus, "Buster" Johnson and Henry Busse
      - The wang wang blues. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1921. (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Muir, Lewis, William Tracy and Ballard MacDonald
      - Play that barber shop chord. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1937., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Muir, Lewis F. and L. Wolfe Gilbert
      - Waiting for Robert E. Lee. Chicago: La Salle Music Pub., Inc., 1939. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Mullins, John
      - Company's comin'. New York: Earl Barton Music, Inc., 1954. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Murray, Fred and R.P. Weston
      - I'm Henry the VIII, I am. New York: Miller Music Corp., 1910. (Box-folder 438/2, 509/1)
    - Msarurgwa, August and Tom Glazer
      - Skokiaan. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1962., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Myddleton, William H. and Sigmund Spaeth
      - Down south. New York: Edward B. Marks Music Corp., 1901. (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Myers, Sherman and Chester Wallace
      - Moonlight on the Ganges. Campbell, Connelly & Co., Ltd., 1942. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Myrow, Gerald
      - Dig-a-dig-a-dum-dum. New York: Plymouth Music Co., Inc., 1959. (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Myrow, Josef and Mack Gordon
      - What did I do?. New York: Triangle Music Corp., 1947. (Box-folder 438/2)
      - Worry about tomorrow, tomorrow. New York: Ramrod Music, Ic., 1956. (Box-folder 438/2)
    - Nascimbene, Mario
      - Song of the barefoot Contessa. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1954. (Box-folder 438/3)
    - Nakamura, Hachidai and Rokusuke Ei
      - Sukiyaki (My first lonely night). Hollywood: Beechwood Music Corp., 1963. (Box-folder 509/2)
    - Napoleon, Phil, Frank Signorelli and Roy Jacobs
      - Anything. New York: Peer International Corp., 1929. (Box-folder 509/2)
    - Nathan, Lloyd
      - My daddy is a soldier. West Los Angeles: Halliburton Music Inc., 1965. (Box-folder 438/3)
    - Nelson, Ozzie
      - I'm looking for a guy who plays alto and baritone and doubles on a clarinet and wears a size 37 suit. New York: Edward B. Marks Music Corp., 1940. (Box-folder 438/3)
    - Nelson, Portia
      - Nee-no-nah-nee. Los Angeles: Nelco Music, 1962. (Box-folder 438/3)
    - Nelson, Steve and Jack Rollins
      - Frosty the snowman. New York: Hill and Range Songs, Inc., 1950. (Box-folder 509/2)
    - Nevin, Ethelbert and Eugene Field
      - Little boy blue. New York: G. Schirmer, 1891. (Box-folder 509/2)
    - Newton, Eddie and T. Lawrence Seibert
      - Casey Jones. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1937., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/3)
    - Nicholls, Horatio and Edgar Leslie
      - Among my souvenirs. New York: DeSylva, Brown & Henderson, Inc., 1927., 2 copies (Box-folder 509/2)
    - Noble, Ray
      - Cherokee. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1938., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/3)
      - I hadn't anyone till you. New York: ABC Music Corp., 1938. (Box-folder 438/3)
      - The very thought of you. New York: M. Witmark & Sons, 1934., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/3)
    - Nolan, Bob
      - Cool water. New York: Hill and Range Songs, Inc., 1936. (Box-folder 509/2)
    - North, Alex and Hy Zaret
      - Unchained melody. New York: Frank Music Corp., 1955. (Box-folder 438/3)
    - Nutile, E. and F. Russo
      - Mamma mia, che vo' sape'?!. Milano: Edizioni Curci, 1942. (Box-folder 438/3)
    - Oakland, Ben and Oscar Hammerstein
      - I'll take romance. New York: Bourne, Inc., 1937., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/4)
    - O'Brien, Billy and Raymond Wallace
      - With my shillelagh under my arm. New York: Pickwick Music Corp., 1936., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/4)
    - O'Connor, Shamus and Stamford
      - MacNamara's band. New York: Jerry Vogel Music Pub. Co., 1917. (Box-folder 509/3)
    - O'Daniel, W. Lee
      - Beautiful Texas. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co., Inc., 1933., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/4)
    - Offenbach, Jacques
      - Choruses from "La belle Helene". New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., 1948. (Box-folder 509/3)
    - O'Hara, Geoffrey
      - One world. New York: Bourne, Inc., 1945., 2 copies (Box-folder 509/3)
    - Olcott, Chauncey, Ernest R. Ball and Rida Johnson Young
      - Mother Machree. New York: M. Witmark & Sons, 1910. (Box-folder 509/3)
    - Oliver, Sy and James Young
      - 'Tain't what you do. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1939. (Box-folder 438/4)
    - Olman, Abe and Jack Yellen
      - Down by the O-hi-o. Chicago: Forster Music Pub. Inc., 1920. (Box-folder 438/4)
    - Olshey, Alex, C. Towber and Don Raye
      - I love you much too much. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1940. (Box-folder 438/4)
    - Original Dixieland Jazz Band
      - Tiger rag. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1917. (Box-folder 509/3)
    - Ornadel, Cyril and Leslie Bricusse
      - If I ruled the world. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1963. (Box-folder 438/4)
    - Ornadel, Cyril and David Croft
      - Friends. London: Chappell & Co. Ltd., 1956. (Box-folder 509/3)
    - Ory, Edward "Kid" and Ray Gilbert
      - Muskrat ramble. New York: George Simon, Inc., 1926. (Box-folder 438/4)
    - O'Shea, Eamonn
      - Come down the mountain Katie Daly. Dublin: Glenside Music Pub. Co., 1961. (Box-folder 509/3)
    - Ostrovsky, Arkadi, Lev Oshanin and Tom Botting
      - May there always be sunshine. New York: Leeds Music Corp. (Box-folder 509/3)
    - Owens, Tex
      - The cattle call. (Box-folder 509/3)
    - Palmer, Jack and Clarke Van Ness
      - Silver dollar. (Box-folder 509/4)
    - Palmer, Jack and Spencer Williams
      - Everybody loves my baby. New York: Pickwick Music Corp., 1924. (Box-folder 438/5)
      - I found a new baby. New York: Pickwick Music Corp., 1926. (Box-folder 438/5)
    - Paoli, Gino and Alec Wilder
      - Senza fine. New York: Ludlow Music, Inc., 1962. (Box-folder 438/5)
    - Parker, Eula
      - The village of St. Bernadette. New York: Ludlow Music, Inc., 1959., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/5)
    - Parnes, Paul and Paul Evans
      - Happiness is. New York: Mills Music, Inc., 1965., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/5)
    - Partichela, F. A.
      - Popular Jarabe Tapatio. New York: Edward B. Marks Music Corp., 1933. (Box-folder 509/4)
    - Pease, Harry, Ed G. Nelson and Harry Tobias
      - All for the love of Mike. New York: Leo Feist, Inc., 1922. (Box-folder 509/4)
    - Penn, Arthur A.
      - Smilin' through. New York: M. Witmark & Sons, 1919. (Box-folder 509/4)
    - Penniman, R., D. LaBostrie and Joe Lubin
      - Tutti frutti. New York: Criterion Music Corp., 1955. (Box-folder 509/4)
    - Pepin, Amy
      - The lovers eye. (Box-folder 438/5)
    - Pepin, Art and Fielding Griggs
      - Dreamby. (Box-folder 509/4)
    - Pesce, Lina
      - Bem-te-vi atrevido. New York: Peer International Corp., 1940. (Box-folder 509/4)
    - Petrie, H. W. and Arthur J. Lamb
      - Asleep in the deep. New York: M. Witmark & Sons, 1920. (Box-folder 509/4)
    - Petrillo, Caesar, Milton Samuels and Nelson Shawn
      - Jim. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1941. (Box-folder 438/5)
    - Petty, Norman
      - Almost paradise. New York: Peer International Corp., 1956. (Box-folder 509/4)
    - Philippe-Gerard, M. and Johnny Mercer
      - When the world was young. New York: Criterion Music Corp., 1950. (Box-folder 509/4)
    - Piantadosi, Al., Joe Gooswin and Ed. Rose
      - Baby shoes. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co. Inc., 1916., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/5)
    - Pinkard, Maceo
      - Don't cry, little cry, don't cry. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co. Inc., 1918., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/5)
    - Pinkard, Maceo and Billy Rose
      - Here comes the show boat. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co. Inc., 1918., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/5)
    - Pinkard, Maceo, William Tracy and Doris Tauber
      - Them there eyes. New York: Bourne, Inc., 1930. (Box-folder 509/4)
    - Pober, Leon
      - Tiny bubbles. New York: Granite Music Corp., 1966. (Box-folder 438/5)
    - Pockriss, Lee and Anne Croswell
      - All for you. New York: Edward B. Marks Music Corp., 1963. (Box-folder 438/5)
      - I know the feeling. New York: Edward B. Marks Music Corp., 1963. (Box-folder 438/5)
      - Make a friend. New York: Edward B. Marks Music Corp., 1963. (Box-folder 438/5)
      - The only one. New York: Edward B. Marks Music Corp., 1963., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/5)
      - Tovarich medley. New York: Edward B. Marks Music Corp., 1963. (Box-folder 509/4)
      - Uh-oh. New York: Edward B. Marks Music Corp., 1963., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/5)
      - Wilkes Barre, Pa. New York: Edward B. Marks Music Corp., 1963., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/5)
    - Pockriss, Lee and Bob Hilliard
      - A kookie little paradise. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co. Inc., 1960. (Box-folder 438/5)
      - My little corner of the world. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co. Inc., 1960. (Box-folder 438/5)
    - Pockriss, Lee and Fred Tobias
      - It's a good thing. Hollywood: United Artists. (Box-folder 438/5)
    - Pola, Eddie and George Wyle
      - I said my pajamas. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1950., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/5)
    - Pola, Edward, Franz Steininger and Mort Dixon
      - Marching along together. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1933. (Box-folder 509/4)
    - Porter, Cole
      - All I've got to get now is my man. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1940. (Box-folder 438/5)
      - Another op'nin', another show. New York: T.B. Harms Co., 1949. (Box-folder 509/5)
      - Anything goes. New York: Harms Inc., 1934. (Box-folder 509/5)
      - At long last love. New York: Chappell & Co., Inc., 1938. (Box-folder 509/5)
      - Blow, Gabriel, blow. New York: Harms Inc., 1934. (Box-folder 509/5)
      - Brush up your Shakespeare. New York: T.B. Harms Co., 1949., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/5)
      - Cherry pies ought to be you. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1950. (Box-folder 438/5)
      - Don't fence me in. New York: Harms Inc., 1944. (Box-folder 509/5)
      - Find me a primitive man. New York: Harms Inc., 1929. (Box-folder 438/5)
      - Get out of town. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1938. (Box-folder 438/5)
      - Girls. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1944. (Box-folder 438/5)
      - Les girls. New York: Buxton Hill Music Corp., 1956. (Box-folder 509/5)
      - Hey, babe, hey!. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1936. (Box-folder 438/6)
      - I get a kick out of you. New York: Harms Inc., 1934., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/6)
      - I love Paris. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1953. (Box-folder 438/6)
      - I loved him (but he didn't love me). New York: Harms Inc., 1929. (Box-folder 509/5)
      - I've got to keep my eyes on you. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1939. (Box-folder 438/6)
      - I've got you under my skin. New York: Chappel & Co., Inc., 1936. (Box-folder 438/6, 509/5)
      - In the still of the night. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1937. (Box-folder 438/6)
      - It's all right with me. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1953. (Box-folder 438/6, 509/5)
      - It's de-lovely. New York: Chappel & Co., Inc., 1936. (Box-folder 509/5)
      - Just one of those things. New York: Harms Inc., 1935. (Box-folder 438/6)
      - The laziest gal in town. New York: Harms Inc., 1927. (Box-folder 509/5)
      - Let's be buddies. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1940. (Box-folder 438/6)
      - Let's do it. New York: Harms Inc., 1928. (Box-folder 509/5)
      - Let's fly away. New York: Harms Inc., 1930. (Box-folder 438/6)
      - Let's not talk about love. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1941. (Box-folder 438/6, 509/5)
      - Looking at you. New York: Harms Inc., 1929. (Box-folder 438/6)
      - Miss Otis regrets. New York: Harms Inc., 1934. (Box-folder 438/6)
      - Night and day. New York: Harms Inc., 1932. (Box-folder 438/6)
      - Ridin' high. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1936. (Box-folder 438/6)
      - Silk stockings. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1954. (Box-folder 438/6)
      - True love. New York: Buxton Hill Music Corp., 1955. (Box-folder 509/5)
      - Two little babes in the wood. New York: Harms Inc., 1928., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/6)
      - What is this thing called love?. New York: Harms Inc., 1929. (Box-folder 509/5)
      - Where, oh where. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1950. (Box-folder 438/6)
      - Who wants to be a millionaire. New York: Chappell & Co. Inc., 1955. (Box-folder 438/6)
    - Presley, Elvis and Vera Matson
      - Love me tender. New York: Hill and Range Songs, Inc., 1956. (Box-folder 438/6)
    - Press, Jacques and Eddie Cherkose
      - Breathless. New York: Porgie Music Corp., 1942. (Box-folder 438/6)
    - Previn, Andre, Betty Comden and Adolph Green
      - Time for parting. New York: Loew's Inc., 1954., 2 copies (Box-folder 509/5)
    - Previn, Andre and Dory Langdon
      - Christmas love. Hollywood: Andor Music Co., 1959. (Box-folder 438/6)
      - Control yourself. Beverly Hills: Artists Music Inc., 1962. (Box-folder 509/5)
      - The faraway part of town. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co. Inc., 1960., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/6)
      - Like love. Hollywood: Andor Music Co., 1960. (Box-folder 438/6)
    - Price, Leo and John Marascalco
      - Send me some lovin'. Hollywood: Venice Music, Inc., 1957. (Box-folder 509/5)
    - Prima, Louis
      - Sing, sing, sing. New York: Robbins Music Corp., 1936. (Box-folder 509/5)
    - Prince, Hughie and The Andrew Sisters
      - Sweet Molly Malone. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1940. (Box-folder 509/5)
    - Prince, Hughie, Marcia Neil and Philip Broughton
      - Funny. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co. Inc., 1962., 2 copies (Box-folder 438/6)
    - Puccini, Giacomo and John Gutman
      - Vissi d'arte, vissi d'amore. New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., 1956. (Box-folder 509/5)
    - Quadling, Lew and Jack Elliot
      - Sam's song. New York: Sam Weiss Music Inc., 1950. (Box-folder 509/6)
    - Raksin, David
      - Laura. New York: Twentienth Century Music Corp., 1945. (Box-folder 509/7)
    - Raskin, David and Mark David
      - Love has many faces. New York: Columbia Pictures Corp., 1964. (Box-folder 439/1)
    - Rand, Lionel and Ian Grant
      - Let there be love. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co. Inc., 1940., 2 copies (Box-folder 439/1)
    - Rapee, Erno and Lew Pollack
      - Charmaine!. New York: Belwin, Inc., 1926. (Box-folder 509/7)
    - Raph, Teddy
      - The farmer in the dell. New York: Broadcast Music Inc., 1940. (Box-folder 509/7)
    - Rasbach, Oscar and Joyce Kilmer
      - Trees. Los Angeles: G. Schirmer Music Stores Inc., 1922. (Box-folder 509/7)
    - Rascel, R. and Carl Sigman
      - Goodbye to Rome. New York: Hill and Range Songs, Inc., 1954. (Box-folder 439/1)
    - Ravel, Maurice
      - Bolero. Paris: Durand & Co., 1929. (Box-folder 439/1)
    - Ravasini, N. and N. Rastelli
      - Dai che vai... Milano: Music Union, 1958. (Box-folder 509/7)
    - Raye, Don and Gene DePaul
      - The first baseball game. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1948., 2 copies (Box-folder 439/1)
      - He's my guy. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1942. (Box-folder 439/1)
      - I'm in love with you. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1950., 2 copies (Box-folder 439/1)
      - Mister five by five. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1942. (Box-folder 439/1)
    - Raye, Don, Gene DePaul and Pat Johnston
      - I'll remember April. (Box-folder 509/7)
    - Raye, Don and Wesley Wilson
      - Do you call that a buddy?. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1941., 2 copies (Box-folder 439/1)
    - Razaf, Andy and Eubie Blake
      - Memories of you. New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Co. Inc., 1930., 2 copies (Box-folder 439/1)
    - Redding, Edward C.
      - The end of a love affair. New York: Duchess Music Corp., 1950. (Box-folder 439/1, 509/7)
    - Redi, P.G. and Nisa
      - Timida serenata. Milano: Edizioni Curci, 1958., 2 copies (Box-folder 509/7)
    - Redman, Don and Ray Gilbert
      - Cherry. New York: Melody Lane Pub., Inc., 1928. (Box-folder 509/7)
    - Reid, Billy
      - The gypsy. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1945. (Box-folder 439/1)
      - I'm walking behind you. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1953. (Box-folder 439/1)
      - It's a pity to say goodnight. New York: Leeds Music Corp., 1946. (Box-folder 439/1)
      - A tree in the meadow. New York: Campbell-Connelly Inc., 1948., 2 copies (Box-folder 439/1)
    - Reisman, Joe